{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"51.8/0.96",
			"answer":"51.8/0.96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.53/6.8",
			"answer":"3.53/6.8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"644/0.92",
			"answer":"644/0.92",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"504/30",
			"answer":"504/30",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"89.3/1.9",
			"answer":"89.3/1.9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4560/5",
			"answer":"4560/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"85.52/2",
			"answer":"85.52/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"321.3/0.3",
			"answer":"321.3/0.3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.705/5",
			"answer":"3.705/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.6308/2",
			"answer":"0.6308/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}



	]
}